Hello, I'm your host David Bernard and
with me today Revenue Cat CEO Jacob I
biting. Our guest today is Chris Holes,
founder and CEO of Life 360. On the
podcast we talk with Chris about how to
do premium the right way. Drafting a
customer bill of rights to guide product
decisions and why blindly following AB
test results can lead to short-term
gains but undermine your business long
term. Hey Chris, thanks so much for
joining us on the podcast today. Thanks
for having me. And Jacob, always nice to
have you with me today. I'm super
excited to talk to the founder of Life
360. I was at a party, Easter party on
Sunday and I literally saw somebody
using Life 360 and I was like, there's
Life 360. So, and here we are. Was it a
mom? It was a youth like uh somebody
maybe 21 years old. I was like, it's
it's still happening. That is happening
more and more. We we were not
complaining. As we were talking before
the podcast, Life 360 is kind of one of
the slept on giants of the subscription
app industry. You know, it's not
mentioned in the same breath as a Straa,
a Dolingo, and some of those, but it is
an incredible company. And I just
checked this morning, you're on the
NASDAQ and Australian stock exchange
with a 1.8 billion USD market cap. Huge
successful story in the subscription app
space. So, I did want to kick off.
You've been on a lot of other podcasts
and kind of given the full story. I
listen to multiple of those. We can put
links in the show notes if people want
to hear kind of the whole founding story
and all that, but I wanted to get the
summary of it and then we could dive
deeper into the nuts and bolts of
building a great subscription app
business like you have. So, what was the
founding story? Yeah, I'll get the very
quick version and hit on a few things
that are more specific to subscription.
So, very quickly, the early idea was
Hurricane Katrina, help families
reconnect after big emergencies. I had
that idea in college, so about 20 years
ago. I've been doing the company for 18.
We've had our one and only pivot in the
early days was to what we're doing now,
which was something much bigger.
Facebook was getting big for friends.
LinkedIn is getting big for
professionals. We thought like, let's go
after families. That part of our pitch
is very cliche, but our take was
different than everyone else, which was
based on our belief that mobile would
become ubiquitous, which obviously has,
but it was actually controversial way
back then. People didn't think teens
would be using smartphones. That was the
number one reason VCs passed on our seed
round. I think it looked like a
productivity tool, but our insight was
that location was so central to many
communications and safety is something
people you'd pay for, but actually tying
it to premium business models. We
figured out that daily communication
utility, good free engagement platform
paired with safety that people pay for
and that really was our secret
monetization sauce. If you go on either
end, you can you can have problems. So
we're now up to over 80 million active
users, 400 million initial revenue,
growing very quickly. International is
taking off and about 600 employees. So
that was in 2008 or so. When did the
first app come out? 2008, I think. Maybe
launch 2009 or something. We were a
launch app on Android. Okay. Which
David's point of you being like a
sleeper giant. Do you think that's part
of the reason is that you've kind of
been like iOS has fine friends baked in
and if you're a full iOS family that
might be your tool of choice? We
actually do better in iOS every region
surprisingly. Really? I mean maybe not
that surprising to me, but I think like
the tech press tends to have a still
like an iOS bias, right? If it's not
Apple, they tend to overlook things. And
I I always wondered if that was I think
that's it. I think we are an example of
being in an unaned category from a VC
standpoint. Now that we're public, it's
a kind of a different ballgame. But I
think for whatever reason, VCs just
assumed our category was not a real one.
and it was a feature not a platform and
I still sometimes wonder why we are kind
of still relatively speaking so under
the radar. I don't really mind because
we have almost no competition which is
weird. Yeah. I also not to get too much
about stock but you guys have one of
these rare stocks that's kind of not
looked totally battered over the last
decade or five years or so and I always
feel like the overfocused on companies
like they tend to just swing around with
the the whims of the market. Yeah. I
mean, we've swung, but we never were
overvalued. So, it's more frustrating.
We We were trading like at 1x revenue at
the peak of the doldrums for no good
reason. Maybe 2x revenue, whatever it
was. But it was it was weird. But people
overlook companies that are not in hot
verticals. I think location now is
finally becoming a thing that people are
not creeped out by. But I I think people
are almost uh only bad parents and bad
families use location sharing. It's
creepy. I think that was more Yeah. Oh.
Oh, right. just like the concept of like
spying on your kids. But yeah, I think I
mean I think about it now. I have a I
have a six-year-old and I'm like I'm
going to chip her. I'm going to know
where she's at until she's 17 and 360
days like years old. You know what I
mean? But it's not actually that
invasive, honestly. It's better if you
use it properly. You can give your kids
more freedom and not worry. The real
helicopter parents are the ones that are
like following them around and
interfering with their activities. We're
sort of just saying go have fun and and
we're actually a way to give kids more
freedom if used appropriately and we
have a big enough user base some parents
do go over the top and I feel bad about
that. But you also exist in kind of an
interesting place that like revenue cat
does too which is like because Apple's
fine friends is so verticalized and like
has no interoperability. It creates an
opportunity for a business like life 360
to become a platform because it's not
locked into these like phones, right? is
like there's a lot of conversations now
about antitrust and these platforms
being locked down. Sometimes the
lockdown actually creates opportunities
for companies to like you know overcome
that lockdown which is your your case. I
feel good about that for our long term
specifically in Europe but surprisingly
we do way better in these iOS heavy
regions and actually to tie it back to
your earlier point I think most of the
world has not woken up to location
sharing. it's many years behind and I
and I think it was fine my even though
find my launched five years after we
were out it really helped us because it
reduced the stigma that was there. So as
of now we actually see it the inverse
where someone's using fine my they've
got over the hump that this is a real
need and then we're just so much better
for our vertical that it doesn't hurt
us. That could change. We don't want to
live we want to be sensitive and not
drink our own Kool-Aid. Apple could get
better. They are getting better. They're
waking up to location. But yeah,
historically, I think it's just actually
interesting for smaller startups that
Apple in your space with a mediocre
product can actually be a good thing.
It's so much easier to be like, it's
find my butt better, right? I can't
imagine how you guys pitched before that
be like, "It's a panopticon for your
family. We know where they are." You
know what I mean? It was kind of hard,
honestly, because people did not. It was
just that for anyone under I'm 41 so I'm
kind of on that tipping point but anyone
under 30 probably doesn't realize just
what the attitudes to the location were
when it came out. I mean I'm 37 and I
remember when like you couldn't even
have a phone to know where people were.
You know what I mean? If you weren't at
your home at the landline like you were
you were unfindable, you know? And that
changed in a decade. It's crazy. And
people said cell phones were invasive
because you could never just you're
always going to be findable. And
relatively they were right. like he went
from like unto unfindable to now I could
call you at any time and you know it's
more the relatives that freak people out
but I don't think anybody who uses these
like location technologies within their
family can say they're not like valuable
and and lifeenhancing and stuff. Yeah. I
mean life is a double-edged sword with
most technologies but you can't put the
toothpaste back in the tube and right
people are going to use it. Yeah. you're
not going to get people off the internet
and we have Leites and Menanites and
Amish who've all made decisions not to
embrace technology and that's genuinely
okay but you do you but we can't stop AI
as an example it's wishful thinking so
get on a whole other tangent there but
it's like we're creating AI race because
we know if we stop the other guy will do
it and so it's just going to keep going
so I think that's just a general theme
of life well you've hit on like five
different topics I want to go deeper on.
But the first one I wanted to go a
little deeper on was you you mentioned
the premium product. And I think this is
something that a lot of folks get wrong
and struggle with. If you want to become
a big app, you almost have to be you
pretty much have to be premium. You have
to have some experience that's going to
retain users who don't pay. And then,
you know, to build a great recurring
subscription business, you've got to
have features that people are willing to
pay for. but getting the balance just
right where you don't ostracize the free
users where they still have a really
fantastic experience but then you have
paid features that actually attract
people to spend. So how have you thought
about this and how have you structured
the premium over time and then has that
evolved? It's one of the things that we
locked in on early on and just haven't
really deviated at all and now we're 18
years into this thing. But ignore our
early couple years. We just trying to
figure things out. We didn't know what
we were doing and the industry was nent.
But what we realized was to your your
point, we will only succeed as a
business if we're premium. I'm not a
purist at all in that regard, but our
belief was that location was going to be
huge. all the carriers were offering
competing products and back in the day
also the younger entrepreneurs probably
be surprised like AT&T and Verizon like
if they had a product there's a threat
to you and how could we compete with
these giants and so we we felt like the
only way you can do that was giving away
a better product for free and that is
what over the top meaning just going
direct to the app stores not to the
carriers I don't know if people still
use that terminology I haven't heard
that in a
while We're all dating ourselves.
Yeah, we kind of felt like we had to.
And so our view is roughly like let's
not even worry about monetization until
we hit 10 million active users. We
probably pushed it later than most
people and that was somewhat arbitrary.
But also in the early days of
subscription, it was way harder to get
people to sign up and there was no inapp
purchase. There weren't even push
notifications. So it's a it's a
different era. But the general view was
for a product like ours which we
correctly identified would actually be a
commodity. Find my came out later. Like
location's everywhere. We would be dead
in the water if we tried to or charge
for our product early on. Now we
actually probably could. There is some
conversation like when do we go to
harvest mode? I would not be the right
CEO for that cuz I'm sort of a product
purist, but we can talk about a little
bit later, but I think once you have
someone on a subscription, you can
actually really really squeeze them if
you want to. We haven't done that. I
don't think that's we're trying to build
a product and brand and platform that
people love, which means you want to
keep a pretty big That's a viral
product, right? So like yeah we want we
need people to love us and we need to
feel like a really good deal and we've
been fortunate our our user base is so
big now we have a lot more flexibility
but going back to the original question
our founding story was around safety and
hurricane Katrina but we very quickly
realized out of sight out of mind and so
you talk about these things people would
want oh like we use that we pay for it
people say yes but they wouldn't so the
thing we realized with location that was
like a 10 time a day use case and people
actually will pay for safety but they
need to be reminded of it and can't
forget about it. So, we basically locked
in on this strategy of you free
location, pay for safety, and it was the
combo of the thing that engages you,
keeps you top of mind, brings you back
again, and then peace of mind that
people pay for. And they're not BS peace
of mind like stuff people actually use.
And we do limit some of the free
features like location history and all
that. But the general theme been ch more
and more challenges get bigger like the
core has to give real value to our
customers not kind of fake value but
like real real value forever for free
period and we actually recently just
wrote a bill of rights for our free user
because it so easy to chip into that
especially because we have the brand and
platform and then you're never going to
know if you pushed it too far with data.
Well, and you have 600 employees and
you've got like a mandate from public
markets to increase revenue and like
it's easy to be like extractive versus
like value creative, right? get it.
We're like the bigger you get, the more
specialized people get and it's just
very hard to keep that focus and and
it's a bit religious because sometimes
people push on me like well we did this
thing look at their attention it's fine
see like you're not being data driven
like smart people might disagree but for
what we're trying to do there's a
gestalt effect and like you just at some
point you've taken this away you've
taken that away you've taken that away
and I don't think we would ever just
fall off a cliff I think we would just
see that people are using find my more
and the prior strategy of just being a
whole lot better is not quite working
and people aren't raving about us
because they're just feeling chipped
away at. Nobody runs a hold out group
long enough to see the cumulative effect
of that. Well, I don't think you can
hold out the hold out group long enough
because I would agree any one feature
you run the hold out group and it
doesn't do anything. You need to run
hold out for a half a decade. You know
what I mean? And with 20 features in a
bucket and it's coming over time. So,
it's almost impossible. So, we we made a
free user bill of rights. It's a that's
a recent thing. I'm curious if it will
work. Is it for internal purposes only,
or are you sharing it with customers,
too? It's not secret, but it's it's
internal. So, it's kind of like, hey,
this is our constitution. Period. Do not
argue with the constitution. Sorry, that
sounds too kind. It's more and we can
always revisit it. It's not Sure. Well,
you can.
Yeah. I'm trying not to be that top.
It's more like this is just the
lifeblood of who we are. This is a thing
that unless it's kind of formally
changed at the kind of exact level got
to believe the religion. I think a lot
of like product people in the trenches
are not all that religious to use the
word again about what they think but you
know they just if you give them some
guardrails and say like hey this is what
we want to do helps to harmonize like a
bigger broader strategy. So ask me a
year if it worked. I don't know. Can you
give an example of what some of the
rights are on the bill? One is just to
start with the most important like we've
basically had location history the core
map location history and place alerts
they must be free doesn't mean we can't
move the pay wall a bit but like real
value there no deceptive tactics around
and dark patterns is another one I could
probably pull it up but the real anchor
is all just around like the free is
lifeblood do we are these are the things
that differentiate us from Apple and
don't touch them we don't tricker
customers we're very transparent when we
do changes we're going to notif people
and not spring it on them because it's
if you're kind of AB testing an early
app like whatever but we're trying to
build this kind of bigger thing you
can't jerk people around in the same
way. Yeah. And I mean you think of like
how Apple you know manages product or
historically like they have a very like
it's a very coherent vision about how
they interact with their customers and
market and bring things. I have a
similar version. I've never made it
public to the team. I probably should
but I call I have a doc of hot dogs.
Like do you hear the Costco hot dog
story? Like you'll never change the
price. Yeah. It's a $149. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. And it's like doesn't matter
if we're losing margin on doesn't
matter. It's always going to be a $149.
It'll And so I have a list of those. I
have a list of uh like things that we
will never touch kind of for me and
Miguel more than anything. But I think
it's important to write those down or
otherwise. Yeah, you're right. It's like
the even you write them down though.
It's just like it's very very hard
because I don't think the purity is a
bit of a religious belief. Yeah. Well,
yeah. And somebody has to enforce it to
some degree, right? Like somebody has to
be like wait like did this violate I
assume you don't have a court system
within life 360. So somebody has to be
like monitoring. No, I think the bigger
thing though is what do we exude as a
company and it's definitely easier for
small startups to be user centric. Then
you get bigger the pressures get bigger
and bigger. Little off topic. One thing
I think young entrepreneurs might not
realize when they think about like
product managers or product they think
about people are probably craftsmen who
build stuff. As companies get bigger,
product managers are they often aren't
builders at all. They're kind of like
aligning on strategy. They might be more
process people. So it's been interesting
that later stage companies like yeah
product managers might not even be able
to build a darn thing. Doesn't mean
they're bad but the craft changes.
They're certainly going to bring a
different set of like personal values
right to the process of building stuff.
Yeah. Something you touched on there was
something I've actually been talking a
lot more about privately and a few times
even on the podcast is that these dark
patterns, you know, as you said tricking
users. any one tactic in isolation could
maybe be justified. Oh, you know, the
call to action button doesn't really say
exactly, you know, it doesn't say
subscribe, it says continue. And it's
like, well, I mean, that's kind of an
industry standard thing now. It's like
people get it, they still have to go
through the Apple flow or, you know, the
price. I've been seeing more and more
apps put the price further and further
away from the call to action button. And
those are like really subtle. It's like
any one of those. It's like that's not a
dark pattern. that's not really tricking
users, but when you start stacking up a
lot of these growth hacks one after the
other after the other, I think people
are underestimating what it feels like
to the people going through the app. And
to your point earlier, you don't see
that in the data because you still get
the convert. You don't see that in the
short term. You see that over like you
were saying, you'd need to do a fiveyear
hold out to really understand how users
feel about your brand and product.
Theoretically, you could do the hold
out. practically you couldn't because
again like you're changing 30 different
things and so you could say we're going
to keep the app from 2025 and we're
going to do a version we don't change at
all to the version of 2030 but then what
about all the improvements there so
you're never going to be able to tease
it out and so it's not about being data
driven I actually think you're being
more data driven to acknowledge the
limits of data and so many people think
they're being data driven by looking at
first order data even with a uh a flimsy
understanding of significance sometimes
right and be like Oh, it's a tenth. It's
a tenth of a point and the significance
calculator says it's six sigma or
whatever and you're just like, well,
let's think about it. We actually
haven't had that problem in terms of
looking at data for whatever reason. One
of my pet peeves, I'm actually going to
send this interview to I'm glad we're
doing this because it's kind of all my
thoughts I can send to our team and just
they can get my We're doing internal
comms for the for Life 360 team. Yes,
exactly. This will actually be a bit of
internal comms. I hate when we do tests
based on percent of user base. I hate
it. Oh, like on just on a subset of the
user race. You mean no that we instead
of n we do percent. We're testing this
with 50% of people, 10% of people, 2% of
people. And I say for our size base, we
can you can round us to 100 million. And
then people say, well, we we need 20% to
get statistical significance. Well,
that's 20 million people. So, are you
saying a company that doesn't have 2,000
people, they just literally can't test?
I still see this happen again and again
and again and again. And I think what it
does do is actually stops people from
doing smart tests because if you want to
do like a paint a door test, paint a
door from dual know like it's basically
fake. You click it and it breaks or you
have made some graceful failure. You
should be able to do that on 100 people
or 10 people and well then we're not
going to get enough uh predictive power.
But I'm kind of okay and I paint a door
that you get like 70% certainty. Yeah.
Well, you get enough predictive power if
it's a powerful enough change. You know
what I mean? 100 people with a big
change, you'll see it. Yeah. Exactly. or
enough just like if we're just doing a
paint a door then we'll do the real test
but this idea that we need statistic
like people need to really understand
what they're testing and when. So sure
if we're trying to like change some
header and some text yeah it's lowrisisk
roll out to everyone and you're kind of
okay kind of picking up
a.1% thing but if you're trying to try
something really new or build a lot like
do the paint a door to 100 people but
don't tell me we're going to do it 1%.
Then you're showing it to almost a
million people. Yeah. Yeah. The percents
get much bigger, right? But I think
people just assume 1%'s small, 50 is
big. And there are times you want to do
like if you're doing a roll out, we do
do like 1 5 10 50 because that's more
server traffic. And well, because you're
on your way to 100, right? Yes. Exactly.
If we're on our way, but I call that is
a roll out, not a test. And again, if
it's and if it's like email headline
copy, sure, like do the percents because
it really doesn't matter. But what are
you testing? Why? What's the right
methodology? like think critically,
think first principles. Don't just
follow a playbook. But I guarantee I'll
show this internally and then I'll go
back to say we need to test 1% and you
got to put in the bill rights. No
percents. No percents. Yeah. Do you do a
lot of like qualitative like let's say
you run a test on 100 people fake door
test. Do you then get this try to get
those folks on the phone or like is that
part of your process? Some people as
we've grown we kind of let more
individual teams do their thing. I
probably spoke to users less than most
would suggest. I'm not saying in a good
way. I probably should have done more of
that. I think I have naturally been
gifted at sort of like putting myself in
someone else's shoes. And I literally
close my eyes and I try to think like if
I'm who I do it literally like what am I
what how am I going to react to this
thing? What I'm going to do? Like not me
but the the customer and the Rick Rubin
method, right? You just like close your
eyes. The famous producer who just
doesn't play any instruments, doesn't
really do. He just like kind of feels it
and like knows what to do. Every great
consumer founder I've worked with has
always had a really both like
emotionally empathetic like ability but
then also like they're very analytical
about that. You know what I mean? They
can like put themselves mechanically
into the mindset of many different
people. And like when I was working
consumer, I sometimes found there's so
many voices that like individual
conversations can sometimes be
misleading because like there's a lot of
variance and behaviors and like it's
very unlikely that you personally are
all that close in characteristic to the
person that you're selling to and
sometimes I think that connection can be
I say start a B2B company then you're
forced to like be in the room with me
all the time. It's actually been a
benefit because it's a little bit
easier. But I was in the same place as
you when I was in consumer like I think
it's still good. I think like and also
like I don't know if you all do surveys
and stuff like that. You talking about
like extending beyond just like pure
like AB test statistical significance on
a binomial experiment. Just sending a
survey to those 100 people that hit the
broken door and being like you know see
if you get any responses. I think
they're all good and you just need to
know why and you don't do it just
because and you're really thoughtful
about it and you don't overly kind of
like saying this is the way other than
our villa rights. You don't don't argue
with that one. But jokes aside, I mean,
we have to say these are the things that
just who we are and but we're being very
self-aware of like these are the
artifacts of religious faith because we
believe they're core to who we are and
these are the things we test and this is
how we think about it. with those free
users, how do you think about monetizing
them and and what has been the path of
monetizing them? I know most recently
you have been working on an in-house ad
network, but have you shown ads this
whole time or like ads are new. We have
some really ugly banners on the home
screen that make me want to I genuinely
have a physical reaction every time I
see them. Well, you just got to
subscribe, Chris. Then they go away.
It's But ads are part of the user
experience. The free user experience. I
removed ads from my side project app
because the user experience of them were
so bad and I went to a hard payw wall
because it really is part of the user
experience. Yeah. So how going back to
just the fuzziness of data the team do
the hold out group and show that the ads
didn't hurt anything at all. I think
that data was actually valid but do that
20 times you don't know but we decided
the
upside was worth it and we are trying to
start this new business and that over
time we can evolve the ad product to
something that customers actually love
or don't even realize it's an ad. So the
banners we have they're horrible I hate
them. I've challenged the team like can
we find in like a year can we not have
ugly banners but really pushing every
day like show that you care about the
customer show you want these gone and
we've done some really cool ones like
when you land at an airport now like hey
David welcome to SFO do you need an Uber
one tap did you do that deal directly
like with Uber we did yeah we have
another one we're announcing which is
very similar where it's not it's
actually good for the customer and
people probably know it's an ad but it's
not interrupting the workflow and if you
actually want to interact with the ad.
It's adding value. I think the company
that did that the best, nothing to do
with subscription, but u credit karma
and credit card ads. Mhm. Yeah. You
don't even know it's an ad, right?
You're just using their website. Well, I
think maybe you do, but like for people
who don't know, Credit Karma is
basically give all your very personal
sensitive information, including your
social. They match you with credit card
offers and your credit score is X. You
live here, this is you want points, you
want travel, whatever. This is the best
card cash back. They just match you with
cards. So it's 100% lead genen.
Everything they match you with is an
actual ad, but to the customer, you are
actually getting matched with a product
and service that is good for you. And so
I think that's very different than
spamming someone and all that. Going
back to Bill of Rights, what we've said
we will not, that's actually in our bill
of rights. I forgot another point. It
was tied with advertising. We will not
get in the way of the job to be done
with an ad. Sure. You know full screen
interstitial 30 seconds to close. Yeah.
What are the ads that upset you so much
then? It's not not the Uber at the
airport ones. Those seem No, that one's
great. I genuinely think I can look
someone in the eye with a straight face
and say I actually think that's giving
you value because if you just want that
one tap it's not hurting you at all. So
we just have these banners. They're it's
just more that like banners are only
good for brand impressions. They don't
really drive performance. So and you
don't get to control probably using an
ad exchange or something like what
brands get pulled in. We are doing that
but we have our own ad unit that does
force people do a little bit to make it
look there. That was one of those just
somewhat arbitrary lines we did as well.
By these are all like things you only
get to do when you have as many users as
life 360, right? Like if you're a random
app, you don't have the leverage to do
this. Yeah, exactly. You would not be
able to. No, you don't have that choice.
So So you never like just installed
Google ADM Mob and just let Google's
serve. I think we did, but we put our
own ad unit and we did some testing
around it and it's just we're using and
we at some point we could actually allow
more of that, but the performance is
actually capped. like put the product
hat back on and like try to think about
what's actually good for users and the
the holy grail for us kind of the credit
karma equivalent is is drive insurance
products for driving because we know how
you drive and people like who wants to
give your data to insurance company
first off most people don't care about
sharing data as much as that's like this
very kind of like tech bubble press
group like most consumers think that
Amazon and Google are like recording
everything you say and doing already and
they say they don't like it but like
it's lost cause yeah it's a lost cause
to them and not that they think they
ever really cared actually I think enjoy
complaining about it. From my
perception, I think that well things
people say they care about. They're not
lying, but what do people actually take
action on? We want to be straight with
our users, but if we were like, I think
people think this is inherently bad
thing without thinking about it. But
imagine if like, hey, Jacob, you are in
the top 5% of drivers. You absolutely
should give your insurance data to
insurance companies. You will be saving
money. And here we can help you. And if
we're like, David, you're in the bottom
10%. You should never ever give your
maybe stop driving. Yeah. Or hey, you
had a DUI. We're gonna match you with
the DUI specialist. Like I don't know.
We That's actually a thing. The hard to
insure people. That's a use like we're
actually helping you with your data and
it's going to be an ad, but think how
good that is. It's not us being sneaky
or like whatever. Like truly, if you're
a top driver, why should you be paying
to subsidize all the bad ones? That will
not feel like an ad when that happens,
but it will be. It'll be like it'll be a
lead genen experience. Yeah, very
similar to Credit Karma, right? Like
except for instead of the finance data,
you're taking in location and transport.
And believe it or not, Credit Karma is
now moving into that same lineup because
they can see they so if you use a Credit
Karma app, um you can do that with the
driving now. And for some insurance like
profile stuff, too. Yeah, they're doing
the exact same thing. And it's not bad
for customers, it's good for customers.
And so we eventually want to get there
and only about one in eight of our
families are paid. So if we get
equivalent performance or sorry if we
get 1/8 performance of monetizing free
users we've essentially doubled our
revenue and then we get the virtuous
flywheel of more to spend on marketing
more to spend on R&D and then just put
more daylight between us and our
competitors. And you said this is fairly
recent. When did you all start playing
with the ads as a revenue generation
thing? About a year ago. Okay. Wow. So
like post after publicly listing and and
all of that. The only revenue before
that was all subscriptions like an app
essentially. did some other more or less
significant revenue I guess. So that's
interesting is cuz like would you say 17
years so 16 years no ads? Yeah we did
have some stuff we were trying to move
into insurance space with all state but
it was sort of so we did have a sliver
of the product there these ugly ads and
we didn't really we still haven't got it
to where we wanted but in terms of like
the kind of traditional ads only been
about bit over a year and you you have
another vector that you have to think
about as a family focused app that kids
and teens are going to be in this app.
How do you think about keeping that
whole experience, including the ads,
familyfriendly? We don't serve ads to
people under a certain age. And we
eliminate huge categories. We still had
a few that have crept in, but we we have
a team that looks at it. We have a
public Slack channel or public in the
company Slack channel for reporting ads
and it's been okay. I really challenge
the team to like get rid of the dumb
banners. Yeah. And a lot of what we also
want to do is we did used to monetize by
selling data. We never had a single
instance of misuse as far as we can
tell. But that kind of got the target on
it from press and regulators. So we
stopped selling raw data. But basically
all that was doing though is helping
people target ads. I personally like
targeted ads. I think it's a good thing.
I kind of joke that the only time I
don't like them is like if my wife's
using the computer, I get a yoga pants
ad.
That's that's not from location. I think
that's usually just IP address and nat
stuff than it is. Yeah. Target ads are
good. like I'd rather relevant ads and I
actually kind of like if I search for a
certain product and I'm not ready to buy
that I know for the next week I'm going
to get their 10 competitors and so we
wanted to do location based we wanted to
empower location based advertising and
so we would do these contracts with
third parties where they would get our
they would get deidentified which is
different than anonymized data feeds
where it's like raw like the GPS points
we would filter out like we try to
filter out sensitive locations but
people would say well in theory someone
could I guess hack the data or breach
your contract and from the third party
you mean? Yeah. And then find out who
you are and do bad things and in theory
that was true but it's very normal to
let third parties have your data like
Google you you guys as an example like
you have it's a good example of how it's
more the feeling of it and the spirit of
it than it is the literal like what's
being shared. I knew like forsquare's
SDK used to monetize that way as well.
There's a lot of companies that would
monetize that way. Was the decision just
like it wasn't worth the PR and like the
explaining and all that stuff for the
revenue or what was the decision to stop
doing it? So, we were able to pivot a
bit and then think longer term, which
actually comes back to the ads piece
where our users never cared, but we
didn't want to keep getting a wave of
bad press and regulators and FDC and all
that. Like, they were actually all the
ones we work with were were fine, but it
was just kind of constant scrutiny that
we didn't need. And our view is that we
could we can move into doing bigger
things in ways that would not spark that
eye. We have one partnership with a
company that does aggregated data and
aggregated is very different than even
deidentified. I'm getting a little
esoteric in the words but like um No,
it's good for this audience. They
they're good. They're good. Yeah. But to
kind of go down those complete raw data
with names, which is always been a no
no. There's deidentified, which is raw
data but no names or emails. There's
anonymize, which is scrambled in a way
where in theory you truly can't find
anything. Period. Period. Period. And
there's aggregated which is even further
which is we're kind of lumping you
together with a whole bunch of stuff. So
we now have a partnership where we do
sell our aggregated data for insights
through a company called Placer.ai. I
think we get like 20some million a year
from them. And it's basically if you are
a re I'm going to give one use case.
You're a retailer. I want to know where
people came from. They came to my store.
What roads did they drive on? Where do
they live? We do it aggregated. So you'd
be able it's by a census block. So 72%
of people come from this census block
and whatever come from this one. But
there's no raw GPS line, all that. And
we still had the press take swipes at
us. This is actually something that
frustrates me about the way Apple
operates. Their privacy stuff is very
ivory tower. It's like there can't be
any possible way for one bit of data to
leak in our like ad tracking. You know,
SKI adi network and things like that are
so ivory tower design versus like the
practicality of a needle in the hay
stack is not worth a Facebook building a
whole infrastructure around finding a
needle here and a needle there that
might happen to leak. Yeah. Meanwhile,
actually incentivizing more privacy
violating systems outside of Apple,
right, by being so limiting. If we're
truly worried about data, like I I think
we are kind of moving to the singularity
and the hive mind and all that. You
should be really scared that these
giants are the ones that have all of it
with complete control. And like don't
you want like kind of the rebel alliance
of smaller companies kind of all using
it and sharing it? So there's a there's
a very weird and arbitrary distinction
like somehow if it's all within your
bucket, it's completely fine. But the
second you do a hook to somebody else,
you're somehow being super dangerous and
risky. To be fair to the other side,
there I think there is some truth that
in like every new industry, there's a
wild west emerges. And so I actually
remember the first time like I met with
a number two guy at Disney in like 2011
or 12. And we were just young at the
time. We were very very small. We built
this really cool tool where you actually
we went right to Disney like look here's
a person watch look here's where they
live and like we walk watch the lines
but it was before there's any regulation
at all and we weren't we weren't even
thinking about the downstream
implications like oh look here's the guy
going to house and like this is where we
live but we just knew so I I do think
that some regulation makes sense but
often times it happens too early and it
just really often favors the giants and
and we're at the point actually kind of
helps us because we can we can have all
the lawyers and yeah, deal with it,
right? 600 people, lots of lawyers, you
can figure it out, right? Navigate it.
Yeah, it's true. It's it's these are
like really interesting because I think
there's a lot of I don't know. I It's
funny you mentioned the selling the data
or the selling the data story. It's very
because because I thought about this
problem for us and actually I didn't
know I written a bill rights, but this
is something I wrote down early is like
we're never going to do that. Not
because like I'm all that moral about
it, but because I knew it would probably
be a press issue and like I just didn't
want to make it a temptation. Like we
could still I could probably find double
our revenue tomorrow if I like we
started selling all of the revenue cat
stuff but I don't want my customers to
have to think about that and we're just
never going to do it you know. Okay
there's no right or wrong answer. What
we have said is we will always be
transparent and that any data product we
have will use it myself and I have I
never opted out and I actually opt into
cross app tracking. I like being
targeted with ads. I'm always like allow
please. And I'm not like a big deal or
anything, but like I have certain more
pe more people after me than the average
person just from like a user base of
millions. I get all sorts of weird crazy
death threats and things and I genuinely
do. But I'm not worried about my data
being out there because the the crazy
dude is not going to be buying data. I I
just don't takes a lot of agency. It's
easy to send a tweet. It's a lot harder
to like, you know, actually hunt
somebody down. What individual without
millions of dollars could find a way to
buy raw data and then I just don't even
know how you'd go about that? I'd have
to set up a fake company first off to
buy it and then then I'd have to commit
fraud. But then I have to become a data
engineer which I am not or find some I
find myself having these conversations
often internally to not related to this
exact question but around like I don't
know maybe it's a contract we're signing
and it's like the lawyers say we can't
sign this thing and it's like can we
just like line up the conditional
probabilities like that would have to
all fire for this to like go wrong.
Anyway, I'm pro data. I think we should
be allowed and open to do more if we
didn't have as as liberal and not
necessarily personal data but like let's
say like copyrighted data for instance
and like we would not have the world of
LLMs that we've invented or been able to
put together in the last few years if we
didn't have a society where like
information was pretty and then there's
obviously there's questions about the
exact legalities but like I think we
could all argue it's probably a net good
thing that this thing was created being
like LLM and AI and right if we had
strangled it we might not have ever ever
invented There's this really good I
forget where I heard of this. Somebody
got Llama 3 running on like a Windows
3.1 machine, which implies like we could
have had this since the 90s. Do you know
what I mean? In theory. But in theory, I
mean, if you can run the model forward
pass, you could you could train it. You
just need more computers and probably
existed at the time. You could have
maybe like uh just guessed weights until
you found the right uh one. But but
anyway, yeah, I don't know. It's there
interesting ethical questions and and I
think something our users are thinking
about and like revenue cut too like
we're quite aware of the we've always
been focused on subscriptions. I still
think that's and it sounds like you too
that's probably best if somebody will
pay for your product like that's the
best way to make money because it's very
aligned. I don't know just to not
exactly pushing on that. I'd be careful
about saying best and what are you
trying to do? What's best for you?
because I I don't think there's a
one-sizefits-all. And even some of the
more growth hacky com like I think a
very valid sub subscription strategy too
is like not exactly premium but it's
basically give people a teaser and
there's been your implicit premium but
so it's not a one-sizefits-all thing. So
I for us it made a lot of sense because
we had a very very very natural
engagement platform with the upsell but
what if we didn't and Right. Yeah. I
guess it's conditioned on that there's
enough people who will pay, right? It's
better that your app exists and is
profitable and is is sustainable than it
is that you use like one specific
monetization method over another, right?
Yeah. Exactly. There could be what are
you trying to do? What are the what are
the specific unique attributes about
your model? Because I think at some
point if our if we get like this
insurance thing working that I'm excited
about like maybe we get rid of the
subscription model alto together and we
give everything away for free because if
we can be the next like all state or
state farm give it all away for free.
Yeah. Yeah. Erode your own margins
before somebody else does. Right. Yeah.
Or or just like just cement our reach.
And uh that is actually something we've
talked about but it's sort of different
stages of the company you'll shift your
strategy and we couldn't have monetized
the data or done insurance early on
because you didn't have the user base
first because it only works when you
have a big user base and you have to
fund yourself and so this evolved and we
we we're 18 years in and it's still
evolving. So, I was going to ask just
off of that, like, yeah, I mean, these
are kind of like problems you only get
the uh privilege to think about when
you've been in it for this long. And I
have to think like there's not too many
It's hard to find CEOs even in like
breakout successes and stuff that go 17
years. And it sounds like you you still
got energy and ideas and stuff like what
has it been like committing to this
project for as long as it has? And like
what keeps you like still energized and
excited to dream about becoming an
insurance company, for example,
in the early days? just really just I'm
someone who kind of lock draw don't quit
and very persistent money was a big
factor for me honestly didn't grow up
with a lot of it weren't weren't broke
but like stability and locking that in
and yeah as my wealth level has
increased and with money out of the
company it's it's hard to keep it going
very few people like whether you love or
hate Elon Musk or Steve Jobs or whatever
like they it was never about the money
for them or it was just about this deep
deep deep drive to maybe it's to win
maybe it's to make the world a better
place. Maybe it's just to build stuff. I
I actually don't have that. So, this is
not my forever and only thing and I kind
of fell into it, but I have a lot of
loyalty to our team, to our investors.
And so, I've I've always said until I
really feel like I'm not needed, I'll
I'll stay. And um I have been trying
actually get less operational these days
and try to focus on the stuff that I'm
more passionate about and do less of the
things that kind of wear me out. Yeah.
But even if you're not leaving, like
that's a thing you need to as a CEO be
doing all the time, right? you like
always need to be layering and or
leveraging and repeatedly because then
it gives you the time to like have the
crazy stupid ideas and things you time
to spend time on that stuff and it gets
harder and harder as you get bigger.
Look at like I remember for a long time
Facebook was buying up a lot of like
seed and series A startups that didn't
quite break out on their own. The idea
is you're going to get these very
entrepreneurial high agency people to
start new product lines at Facebook.
Does any break out and work? Like
Instagram maybe would be the one I would
I'd say well they bought Instagram but
that was a 1.1 billion acquisition but
yeah oh yeah they paid for more than
just the team. Yeah. And just letting
them giving them a budget to build new
products and I I don't think any
actually made it in their own right. I
think they got some really good talent
into other parts of Facebook. But it's
very very hard for companies to do new
things that get bigger. It's almost a
law of nature. And it's frustrating how
much you slow down. But it's also, hey,
the only reason we're here is because of
these laws of nature. Cuz in in a weird
theoretical sense, shouldn't the big
guys just suck up every piece of
opportunity? They have lots of money and
momentum and users, but it's it's just
not how the world works. What do you do
to like kind of fight those laws in
nature internally, like bills of rights,
like things like that? Do you just I
like to just go and blow things up
sometimes. I'm order magnitude smaller.
I am not a natural kind of graceful
leader. I kind of just smash stuff in a
lot and I and I know there in theory is
a better way. Like I think the best way
to lead is clear like be the
inspirational person be kind of really
collected and like have the master plan
execute make people feel good. Clearly
that's the best and I think it does
exist and some CEOs I think are like
like that. I look up to people like Reed
Hastings and all that like good good
human being, composed, thoughtful, not
overly erratic. I think the second best
though is just sheer brute force and
just like get done. Elon's probably
the extreme example of that. You're
making a value judgment there though.
Why do you think it's not the best? I
mean, so many things just can't get
built with that mentality. because I
think it wears out the person doing it
and it wears out the people around them.
And so I think let me I'll go to the
third best when we come back. The third
best is I think where big companies fail
which is just bureaucracy where they
think they're doing it. They're doing
the surveys. They're like making sure
everyone's heard but then you get this
thing where like any one person can say
no but you need 12 people to say yes and
then you just grind to a halt. So, I
have been very much a leader in the
number two category and I'm trying to
get better at moving up the chain and
and this is a sort of an abstract
framework. I'm not necessarily like no
one's in one bucket or the other, but
willingness to pick fights is a lot of
the reason I'm still here. You must
enjoy it a little bit. Not internally. I
don't the results I guess at least,
right? I think people really
misinterpret that about me. I I don't
like conflict. The only time I like
conflict is when I feel like someone
like I can truly put you in a bad person
bucket. So like when people sue us like
patent trolls, I just like where you're
righteous. Yeah. Then then it's really
fun. Yeah. I I can let out my righteous
anger, whatever that means. But no, I I
actually deeply deeply dislike conflict
and I have to have all sorts of
strategies to get around. It's it's
reflexively I'm I'm tough. So it's like
I I'm not cowering, but it doesn't it
takes my energy versus gives it. And I I
hate firing people with a passion. And
my my strategy on that is if I if
someone's not working like an exec I
will tell the board it's not working and
I'll be like I'm telling you now to put
myself in an uncomfortable position. So
when you ask me in a month is it fixed
or is it not I'm going to have a shitty
conversation either way. I've either
either fixed the problem or I'm going to
look really or I'm going to look really
bad to our board that I'm not making
tough decisions. So I think you can
manage your own psychology by putting
yourself between a rock and a hard place
intentionally. the point about like sort
of process death by process right I
think applies at a lot of levels I think
like we kind of touched on it with the
experimentation conversation as well
it's like I think sometimes you can to a
fault ignore the um the intuitive and
the obvious and sort of the common sense
in lie of like oh we have to do it the
right way because there's too much at
stake or like whatever and it turns out
that like especially for compounding
businesses like life 360 or like revity
or like ones that have brands and sort
of like repeatable motions It's very
unlikely you're going to do one wrong
action that's going to like, you know,
maybe you could in a position as a CEO,
but even then if you did something so
off the rails like the board would take
care of it and the company would be back
on, you know, the next day. I think
people fall into a trap of that. It's
like, hey, it's like it's so easy for me
to mess up that like I should just avoid
that at all costs, right? Yeah. We
haven't solved that one fully because we
we do have a few things like we have
life safety related features that really
can't break. We have to be the best at
location. And part of what we do is like
doing it without killing a battery. So
part of one of our challenges like I
actually think killing someone's battery
is it's a one-way door, not a two-way
door. And so we're not like a social
network and they'll never even if you
fix the bug, they will forever feel like
you're killing the battery. And we still
have that from a few handfuls of battery
bugs. Yeah. Well, just think about it
from a from a product mission
perspective. Like somebody's really
unsafe if their phone's dead. You know
what I mean? Like they can't even call
911. So it has been a hard one for us
where we still have some fear I think to
ship. So we are saying these are the
things that can't break. These are
things that can't even going back to
like test like paint a door do it to 100
people don't worry about craftsmanship
like don't be stupid but it's very hard
to have nuance communication at scale.
And so that's why I think you do get
these process like we really do need to
be fanatical about location and battery
not breaking for us. And that needs to
be a big problem when somebody breaks or
aggresses that like that has to be like
the people feel it when we call it
guilty till proven innocent like jump in
like we we're going to chase ghosts 80
90% of the time but the one time we
catch something it's probably going to
the ER right it's like us and uptime
right anything for us that's reliability
related I don't care if it's a one in a
100 that it's a thing we have to chase
it or I won't be able to sleep the time
I've seen Jacob the grumpiest are
around outages and issues that I mean
But th those are our can't break
situations. If I started the game over,
I don't know if I'd do a critical
infrastructure company. I might make
different choices. But I think it's
similar going back to the size of SC
like the average employee is not going
to have that same passion around it
because it's a bystander effect and the
person that can't be the bystanders, the
CEO and the founders, but then you get
the processes to try to acknowledge the
reality that people aren't going to have
the same passion as you. And then you
get the processes that just expand and
expand and expand. And so we definitely
have gone through that with like as we
got bigger we needed a scalable way of
not breaking location. I think we've
flipped way too heavy towards kind of
like too much focus on program
management and things the exp. It's just
a very very hard tradeoff. Yeah. And
it's still I imagine you like every
probably incremental 100 employees you
have to kind of like revisit these
things. They just keep cropping up or
it's uh deja vu every day. But I think
that's but that's part of part of the
just part of it. I think that never
ends. I see it when I look at like Toby
at Shopify like it seems like he's still
fighting some of the same demons that I
feel like I'm fighting now and probably
you're fighting too at three different
scales. I mean I think that's the we
talk about just doing stuff like for
people making apps right like just try
stuff just like do stuff. Don't let your
fears of you know breaking things or
fears of you know whatever like throw it
to 100 people break you know forget
about craftsmanship just get it out
there and like applies to corporate
process it applies to like product
management like just like sort of
entropy can be a very very useful thing
to insert into systems but sometimes
that can taken the other way and I see
that too which is like one of my things
I see I think that's good advice for
founders but I just say oh get it out
there get learnings but you still need
to have a strong intention about what
you're trying to do so like for us like
big northstar our vision. They had to
build things in chunks, but we had a
feature that failed last year and it was
a bummer because like I think the team
was just looking at two week horizons
and there's sort of a northstar of where
they're trying to go, but I think we
just got in our own way around like
testing too much and so it's there's a
lot of nuance in this. I think some
people are naturally good at it. I think
founders usually the ones that get
funding and all that. Like if you've
made it to even series A, you're
probably have some level of outlier gift
there. Not like 0.01% are outlier, but
you're pretty good because you were able
to have that intuition around what
people want and how to build things. But
the average person who's kind of come up
through a different track, they just
don't have those skills in the same way.
They have other skills. Like I I don't
think I would have been promoted up to
the chain. Oh god, no. For me, I like I
was in my that was the highest I was
ever gonna get. Yeah. So, I think I
would have probably had to have been on
a sort of like the super IC path or
start my own thing because I I think I
would have I think people think there's
this linear path from IC to CEO or
whatever, but the skill sets chunk very
very differently. It's kind of their
channels, right? Like a lot of they
don't they don't all terminate in the
same place. You know what I mean? Yeah.
And what makes you good at the next
one's completely orthogonal. So, I think
you can be a good CEO and a bad manager.
I'm legitimately not a very good
manager. Don't Don't tell anybody, but
yeah, same boat. Same boat. Yeah. I
mean, it's it goes to the point there
would be a lot more than there's only
like I looked this up today because I
was doing some research, but there's
only like 3,000 or so companies listed
publicly, at least on the NASDAQ.
There'd be a lot more than 3,000 if if
everybody was good at this, right? Or
everybody everybody had this skill and
it was easy. So, it's just the way of
it. But, I don't know. I think these
talk about just like nuance and and and
just applying a combination, right, of
like the data, your intuition, input
from customers, like you kind of just
have to all take it all in. And I feel
like when you set up orgs and you
specialize and stuff, it kind of goes in
the opposite direction of that. You know
what I mean? Or you have to like create
like really good information flow or
culture probably is the right word,
religion, whatever to like induce that.
I don't think anyone's fully solved it.
You can look at a few companies but it's
very especially for product focus
consumer product focused ones like very
very very few are able to maintain
craftsmanship at scale or craftsmanship
plus rapid innovation you can the
trade-offs are tough or stability and
speed like it's it's easy to be stable
if you're not doing anything. Yeah I I
see I always feel like I'm not sure
those are completely orthot you know
what I mean there's like no physical
reason but there seems to be strong
correlation that they don't often align.
Yeah, I do think the ultimate cliche
answer to all this is just hire really
good people and be ruthless about that.
And I and then also very hard to do and
then it's gotten a lot easier because
there's we've had this market downturn
and now with AI everything's a bit
easier so you can run leaner. But if I
go back to some of the VC advice from we
started in a very different era. It all
holds true today and the vast majority
of it is just team team team. Yeah.
Which culture is like one of these
things like uh that helps that you know
without you in every single interview
closing. Sure. But it is so hard. I
think it sounds easy but like it's not
it's not it's like the hardest. It's
probably the hardest part. Yeah. The
people. Yeah. Always has been. Miguel
says that. My co-founder says all the
time. He's like computers are easy. Like
it's the people that are hard. Product
is easy to some degree too. I guess
product is more people. But yeah. Then
when do you want homogeneity versus
diversity of things? And I'm not talking
in like a identity sense. I'm more
saying like the people who really want
to do AB tests and iterate are usually
not kind of the really craftsman
oriented people who have vision around
it. And they're both important skills
and it's you need both, but then that
makes it harder to kind of have that
especially early on. You don't have a
kind of a central theme around who you
are. Creates a lot of tension too,
right? Like when people have like
somewhat different values, what I've
hope is the point of mission, right?
Like if we can all agree we're on the
same mission and then it can be resolved
and and the tension is good, right? I
feel like tension in in art and most
things like can actually improve the
outcome to some degree. But in theory,
but if you kind of go back to the early
PayPal guys, they like we want everyone
who thinks the same way and acts the
same way because we just was not the
especially early on it was not the time
and place to kind of like have differing
views. It was like we're all thinking
the same way on a mission. It was super
fun to be a fly on the wall listening to
two CEOs, Gab and and I think our a lot
of our audience will be interested to
know because they're either working for
someone like you or aspire to be an
executive at a larger company or grow to
your size. So, I think getting those
kind of insights and getting into your
head a little bit is super interesting.
I was fascinated. But I will say I want
you to introduce me to somebody else on
your team who can go talk about the 10
other topics we had signed up for today.
I'm sure uh I we have we have lots and
going back to the different functions
like we have some very good people who
are very focused on optimizing
subscriptions and they're not
necessarily would even claim to be the
people that would be the kind of the big
product thinkers but when you're at the
scale we have hundreds of millions of
revenue like small improvements and
doing things the right way really really
do matter and even kind of flows that
would I don't even I've looked at that
how do you cancel save flows and like if
someone's about to churn it's not really
about the vision, but like these are
real levers to help and like how do you
make sure Yeah. all because someone's
credit card goes bad, what do you do and
like how do you have a nice way of
reminding someone what they're losing?
So, it's and very very different the
vision side, but very important.
Awesome. Well, as we wrap up, anything
you wanted to share? Uh, we're going to
share a link to the careers page, but
maybe listening to this podcast,
somebody's not going to jump right into
applying to a VP direct report. No, that
says that the right people will. That's
the whole point, David. No, it's true.
I'm I'm getting less operational these
days. So, it's uh you don't have to deal
with me as much as you would have in the
past. Our COO, Lauren, has been taking
on so much for me and she's amazing. If
someone does want to join, we're we're
growing very quickly. We are very
focused on just having the best team.
We've been under the radar for a very
long time, but now that we're in this
world where it's it's not kind of the
go- go days, we're we're almost like a
defensive growth stock. We grow very
predictively. who are very profitable,
very limited marketing budgets. And we
also have been very focused on the free
user. So we we have a lot of room to
grow because we have not been one of
those companies that have gone to the
aggressive harvest mode prematurely,
which is probably some of the stuff we
could talk about in another
conversation. Yeah, that's one of the
things that I wanted to get to and again
we'll just have to have a different
conversation with somebody else on the
team, but you have a huge vision and
you're already expanding into new
vertical. So most people, myself
included, think about Life 360 as like
keep tab on my kids. And my son's on
Android now, so I've been meaning to
install it because I can't get a track
on his location now that he's off the uh
Find My ecosystem. But you have a very
big vision and you're expanding into
Elder Care. Like you said, there's just
so much opportunity. So even though
you're already at a $2 billion
valuationish, there's massive headroom.
So it's like come for the family
location sharing, stay for the world
domination, you know, something like
that. Well, we jokes aside, we want to
be the super app for families and it's
the closest network we all have. And
from the time you have little kids to
aging parents, there are a lot of needs
that we think we can solve. And the
Trojan horse that I think people are
only realizing like a location in and of
itself is a boring commodity, but we
have a app that I think parents are
coming 22 times a day. So we have so
many touch points and we have this data
that really opens up a lot and we're
excited about the next chapter. Yeah,
fascinating company. Well, thanks so
much for joining us and for opening up
so much about how you think about
things. So So thanks. Thank you for
having me.
Thanks so much for listening. If you
have a minute, please leave a review in
your favorite podcast player. You can
also stop by
chat.subclub.com to join our private
community.